Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Latin America Serials TAM.770
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Poetas Cubanos Del Siglo XIX: Cuadernos de Revista Union, Havana, Cuba, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- ¡Presente!: SOA Watch, Washington, DC, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Pueblo y Cultura 9: Consejo Nacional de Cultura, Havana, Cuba, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Quepasa: Quepasa, Syracuse, NY, 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Quincentennial of the Discovery of America: Encounter of Two Worlds: General Secretariat of the Organization of American States, Washington, DC, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 2-3)
- Red de Recursos de Comunicación Alternativa: Cimca, La Paz, Bolivia, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Regeneracion: Regeneracion, Los Angeles, CA, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Report on Guatemala: Network in Solidarity with the People of Guatemala (NISGUA), Oakland, CA, 1987-1997 (Box 21, Folder 7-8)
- Republica Espanola: Accion Republicana Democratica Espanola (ARDE), Mexico, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Resistance Couier: Resistance Publications, Oakland, CA, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Resistencia: Movimiento de Solidaridad con la Resistencia Armada Campesina, Colombia, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Revisita Cubana de Derecho: Instituto Cubano del Libro, Havana, Cuba, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Revista Cenic: Ciencia Biologias: Centro Nacional de Investigaciones Cientificas, Havana, Cuba, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Revista Retorno a Utopia: Revisto Retorno a Utopia, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Revolucion: Revolucion, La Habana, Cuba, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Revolutionary Strategy to Defeat US Intervention: Radio Venceremos System, San Francisco, CA, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- S.O.A. Watch: SOA Watch, Columbus, GA, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Seattle CISPES: U.S. Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador, Seattle, WA, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Sercom: Servicio de Comunication: Centro de Informacion, Investigacion y Documentacin del Uruguay (CIIDU), Montevideo, Uruguay, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Si Se Puede: El Comite De Informacion y Analisis, Santa Barbara, CA, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Sin Fronteras: La Raza de Bronce, Los Angeles, CA, Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Soberania: Organo del Tribunal Antimperialista Centroamericano y del Caribe, Managua, Nicaragua, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Solidaridad: Impreso en IMCO, Parana, Argentina, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Solidaridad Con Chile: World Peace Council, Helsinki, Finland, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Sowing the Oil: Corporate Public Affairs Management Unit, Caracas, Venezuela, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Sunrise: Sunrise, Bluefields, Nicaragua, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Third Congress of the Federation of Cuban Women: Federation of Cuban Women, Havana, Cuba, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Tribu: Instituto Cubano de Estudios Politicos Jose Antonio Echeverria, Union City, NJ, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Tribuna de la Habana: Tribuna de la Habana, Havana, Cuba, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Tribuna del Congreso: Editorial Colombia Nueva, Bogota, Colombia, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Under Construction: Center for Cuban Studies, New York, NY, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Unidad: Federacion de Trabajadores Telefonicos de Cuba en el Exilio, Miami, FL, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Unidad Latina: Comité-Movimiento De Izquierda Nacional Puertorriqueño, New York, NY, 1971-1978 (Box 9, Folder 10-11, Box 10, Folder 1-6, Box 22, Folder 11)
- Union: Union de Escritores y Artistas de Cuba, Havana, Cuba, 1969-1979 (Box 22, Folder 19-20, Box 23, Folder 1-5)
- Union of Latin Radical Americans: Union of Latin Radical Americans, Green Bay, WI, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- United Freedom Front Communique: United Freedom Front, USA, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Update: Center for Cuban Studies, New York, NY, 1979-1983 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Update Central America: Inter-Religious Task Force on Central America, New York, NY, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Update on Guatemala: Committee in Solidarity with the People of Guatemala, New York, NY, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- URNG Boletin Internacional: Unidad Revolucionaria Nacional Guatemala, Guatemala, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- US / Guatemala Labor Education Campaign Update: US / GLEP, Chicago, IL, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- USLA Action Letter: US Committee for Justice to Latin American Political Prisoners, New York, NY, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Van!: Venceremos Brigade, USA, Undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Vanguardia Grafica: Federacion de Obreros de Imprenta de Chile, Chile, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Venceremos Brigade: Educational Commission, New York, NY, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Venceremos Reports: Venceremos Brigade National Office Inc., New York, NY, Undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Venceremos!: Toronto Chilean Association, Toronto, Ontario, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Voces de la frontera: Voces de la Frontera, Austin, TX, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Voices from Columbia: Columbia Media Project, New York, NY, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Voz Fronteriza: Voz Fronteriza, San Diego, CA, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- VOZ Proletaria: Colombian Communist Party, Bogotá, Colombia, 1973-1977 (Box 11, Folder 3-9, Box 29, Folder 7, Box Shared Tamiment 050, Folder 1)
- What Does the CTAL Mean?: Latin American Federation of Labor, Mexico, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Why is the FMLN Fighting?: Radio Venceremos System, San Francisco, CA, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Women's Packet on Chile: Action for Women in Chile, New York, NY, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Working Together: Labor Report on the Americas: Resource Center of the Americas, Minneapolis, MN, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Zapatista Info-Bulletin: Zapatista Solidarity Committee, New York, NY, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 15)